<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ignotis&#39; Blog</title>
    <link>https://dillmo.github.io/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ignotis&#39; Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2015 16:40:56 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://dillmo.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Chrono Warriors Progress Update #1</title>
      <link>https://dillmo.github.io/blog/posts/CWProgressUpdate1/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Nov 2015 16:40:56 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dillmo.github.io/blog/posts/CWProgressUpdate1/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Chrono Warriors code is now officially underway!&lt;/strong&gt; Funnynin and I have
worked hard to prepare Chrono Warriors for collaboration, and it is finally
ready. This first progress check is part of a weekly series that will be
published each Thursday. Each will mention the latest improvements in the game&amp;rsquo;s
codebase.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;new-this-week:d9c61739c30937f4e61f9041e645482e&#34;&gt;New this week&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Got underway with PySFML, a simple multimedia library for use with Python&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Scaffolding for player and movement logic&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Created a basic map using Tiled, an open-source map editor. We are working
hard to add logic for handling Tiled maps. Tiled provides us the flexibility
to easily create new maps with custom tilesets, and is easy to use even for
non-coders.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://dillmo.github.io/blog/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Sep 2015 10:43:24 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dillmo.github.io/blog/about/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;about-my-blog:6083a88ee3411b0d17ce02d738f69d47&#34;&gt;About my Blog&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This blog serves as a repository for all my personal projects. It is designed to
be informal and irregularly updated. As a result, I will use informal language
and be sparse on proofreading. If I err in the grammatical sense, please do not
hesitate to warn me in the comments.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;My blog will never serve ads. However, its comments are powered by Disqus, which
some extensions, especially Privacy Badger, will block for tracking. If you want
to write a comment and cannot find the comment section, please try disabling
your advertisement and tracking blockers first.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&#34;about-me:6083a88ee3411b0d17ce02d738f69d47&#34;&gt;About Me&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Dillon Morse, a junior at the Academy for Science and Design, where I
study computer science, chemistry, and calculus. If you met me online, you
probably know me as Ignotis, an active botmaker on the Awesomenauts forums. I
have a strong interest in artificial intelligence and, more broadly, computer
systems and programming. While I spend most of my free time on personal
projects, I also enjoy casual gaming and action RPGs.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>